export const quiz = {
  totalQuestions: 10,
  questions: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "What is the name of Michael Scott's film?",
      answers: [
        "Threat Level Midnight",
        "Time Bandits",
        "Agent Michael Scarn",
        "Midnight Strike",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Threat Level Midnight",
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question:
        "What is the name of the company that the employees of The Office work for?",
      answers: [
        "Dunder Mifflin",
        "Paper Company Inc.",
        "Staples",
        "Michael Scott Paper Company",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Dunder Mifflin",
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "What is the name of the cat that Angela owns?",
      answers: ["Sprinkles", "Fluffy", "Mittens", "Snowball"],
      correctAnswer: "Sprinkles",
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "What does Dwight grow on his farm?",
      answers: ["Beets", "Carrots", "Potatoes", "Cabbages"],
      correctAnswer: "Beets",
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "Who started the fire in the office?",
      answers: ["Ryan", "Dwight", "Jim", "Michael"],
      correctAnswer: "Ryan",
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "What is Pam's favorite flavor of yogurt?",
      answers: ["Mixed Berry", "Vanilla", "Strawberry", "Blueberry"],
      correctAnswer: "Mixed Berry",
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "What city does Jim move to for his new job?",
      answers: ["Stamford", "New York", "Philadelphia", "Boston"],
      correctAnswer: "Philadelphia",
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "What is the name of the award that Michael Scott created?",
      answers: ["The Dundies", "The Scotts", "The Mifflins", "The Scrantons"],
      correctAnswer: "The Dundies",
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "Who does Michael hit with his car in the parking lot?",
      answers: ["Meredith", "Phyllis", "Angela", "Oscar"],
      correctAnswer: "Meredith",
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question:
        "What is the name of the HR representative who Michael dislikes?",
      answers: ["Toby", "Kevin", "Stanley", "Andy"],
      correctAnswer: "Toby",
    },

    {
      id: 11,
      question: "What is the name of Jim and Pam's first child?",
      answers: ["Piper", "Holly", "Cecilia", "Samantha"],
      correctAnswer: "Cecilia",
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question:
        "What is the full name of the character played by Rainn Wilson?",
      answers: [
        "Dwight Schrute",
        "Dwight F. Schrute",
        "Dwight Kurt Schrute III",
        "Dwight K. Schrute",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Dwight Kurt Schrute III",
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      question:
        "What is the name of Michael Scott's girlfriend who worked in HR?",
      answers: [
        "Jan Levinson",
        "Holly Flax",
        "Karen Filippelli",
        "Donna Newton",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Holly Flax",
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      question:
        "Which branch did Jim transfer to before returning to Scranton?",
      answers: ["Stamford", "Utica", "Buffalo", "Nashua"],
      correctAnswer: "Stamford",
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      question:
        "What song does Michael and Holly perform at the company picnic?",
      answers: [
        "Islands in the Stream",
        "Grease Lightning",
        "Endless Love",
        "Let's Get Physical",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Islands in the Stream",
    },
    {
      id: 16,
      question: "Who is the receptionist after Pam?",
      answers: [
        "Erin Hannon",
        "Angela Martin",
        "Kelly Kapoor",
        "Meredith Palmer",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Erin Hannon",
    },
    {
      id: 17,
      question: "What is Creed's job title?",
      answers: ["Human Resources", "Accounting", "Quality Assurance", "Sales"],
      correctAnswer: "Quality Assurance",
    },
    {
      id: 18,
      question:
        "What game does the office play during a 'Diversity Day' training session?",
      answers: [
        "Guess the Race",
        "Indian Poker",
        "Hold Up the Race Card",
        "Hot Seat",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Hold Up the Race Card",
    },
    {
      id: 19,
      question: "Who bought Michael's 'World's Best Boss' mug?",
      answers: ["Himself", "Pam", "Jim", "Jan"],
      correctAnswer: "Himself",
    },
    {
      id: 20,
      question: "Where do Michael and Jan go for their vacation?",
      answers: ["Bahamas", "Puerto Rico", "Sandals Jamaica", "Mexico"],
      correctAnswer: "Sandals Jamaica",
    },
    {
      id: 21,
      question: "What is the name of the warehouse foreman?",
      answers: [
        "Roy Anderson",
        "Madge Madsen",
        "Darryl Philbin",
        "Lonny Collins",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Darryl Philbin",
    },
    {
      id: 22,
      question: "What is Angela's favorite song?",
      answers: [
        "The Little Drummer Boy",
        "Deck the Halls",
        "Jingle Bells",
        "Silent Night",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "The Little Drummer Boy",
    },
    {
      id: 23,
      question: "Who wins the 'Hottest in the Office' Dundie Award?",
      answers: ["Ryan Howard", "Kelly Kapoor", "Pam Beesly", "Jim Halpert"],
      correctAnswer: "Ryan Howard",
    },
    {
      id: 24,
      question: "What is the name of Michael's boss?",
      answers: [
        "David Wallace",
        "Charles Miner",
        "Josh Porter",
        "Jan Levinson",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "David Wallace",
    },
    {
      id: 25,
      question: "What does Jim send Dwight instead of a message via fax?",
      answers: [
        "Messages from Future Dwight",
        "Invoices",
        "Black Paper",
        "Prank Messages",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Messages from Future Dwight",
    },
    {
      id: 26,
      question: "What is the name of the security guard?",
      answers: ["Jake", "Joe", "Hank", "Earl"],
      correctAnswer: "Hank",
    },
    {
      id: 27,
      question:
        "What is the name of the paper company that takes over Dunder Mifflin?",
      answers: ["Vance Refrigeration", "Sabre", "Staples", "Prince Paper"],
      correctAnswer: "Sabre",
    },
    {
      id: 28,
      question: "Who does Dwight hook up with at Jim and Pam's wedding?",
      answers: ["Angela", "Kelly", "Isabel", "Erin"],
      correctAnswer: "Isabel",
    },
    {
      id: 29,
      question: "What brand of potato chips does Kevin love?",
      answers: ["Pringles", "Ruffles", "Utz", "Lay's"],
      correctAnswer: "Utz",
    },
    {
      id: 30,
      question: "What is the name of Michael's imaginary best friend?",
      answers: ["Todd Packer", "Jimmy", "Tony", "Michael Scarn"],
      correctAnswer: "Jimmy",
    },
    {
      id: 31,
      question: "What is Jan's candle company called?",
      answers: [
        "Serenity by Jan",
        "Jan's Flames",
        "Scents by Jan",
        "Candles by Jan",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Serenity by Jan",
    },
    {
      id: 32,
      question: "What is the name of Michael's nephew who works as an intern?",
      answers: ["Luke", "Danny", "Jeff", "Jake"],
      correctAnswer: "Luke",
    },
    {
      id: 33,
      question: "Who is Pam's first fiance?",
      answers: ["Jim", "Roy", "Danny", "Andy"],
      correctAnswer: "Roy",
    },
    {
      id: 34,
      question: "Which character has a beet farm?",
      answers: ["Stanley", "Dwight", "Jim", "Angela"],
      correctAnswer: "Dwight",
    },
    {
      id: 35,
      question: "What sport does Jim play in the office?",
      answers: ["Soccer", "Basketball", "Tennis", "Volleyball"],
      correctAnswer: "Basketball",
    },
    {
      id: 36,
      question: "What is the name of Pam and Jim's second child?",
      answers: ["Patrick", "Paul", "Philip", "Peter"],
      correctAnswer: "Philip",
    },
    {
      id: 37,
      question: "Who does Michael date from the Utica branch?",
      answers: ["Donna", "Karen", "Holly", "Jan"],
      correctAnswer: "Karen",
    },
    {
      id: 38,
      question: "Who runs the office's 'Fun Run'?",
      answers: ["Jim", "Andy", "Michael", "Dwight"],
      correctAnswer: "Michael",
    },
    {
      id: 39,
      question: "What is the name of Andy's college a cappella group?",
      answers: [
        "The Harmonics",
        "The Nard Dogs",
        "Here Comes Treble",
        "Treble Makers",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Here Comes Treble",
    },
    {
      id: 40,
      question: "What branch does Karen move to after leaving Scranton?",
      answers: ["Buffalo", "Utica", "Akron", "Albany"],
      correctAnswer: "Utica",
    },
    {
      id: 41,
      question: "What is the name of the strain of marijuana that Creed sells?",
      answers: [
        "Dunder Mifflin Special",
        "Northern Lights",
        "Creed's Weed",
        "Hydroponic Pot",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Northern Lights",
    },
    {
      id: 42,
      question: "What does Pam want to be?",
      answers: ["A chef", "An artist", "A writer", "A teacher"],
      correctAnswer: "An artist",
    },
    {
      id: 43,
      question: "What does Michael burn his foot on?",
      answers: ["A George Foreman grill", "A toaster", "A stove", "An iron"],
      correctAnswer: "A George Foreman grill",
    },
    {
      id: 44,
      question: "Who has a heart attack in the office?",
      answers: ["Creed", "Meredith", "Stanley", "Kevin"],
      correctAnswer: "Stanley",
    },
    {
      id: 45,
      question: "What does Pam dress up as for Halloween in Season 2?",
      answers: ["A pumpkin", "A cheerleader", "A cat", "A witch"],
      correctAnswer: "A cat",
    },
    {
      id: 46,
      question: "Which character's mother does Michael date?",
      answers: ["Pam", "Angela", "Phyllis", "Kelly"],
      correctAnswer: "Pam",
    },
    {
      id: 47,
      question: "What is Andy's real first name?",
      answers: ["Jack", "Robert", "Drew", "Walter"],
      correctAnswer: "Walter",
    },
    {
      id: 48,
      question: "What does Michael pretend to fire Pam over in Season 1?",
      answers: [
        "Stealing post-it notes",
        "Not answering the phone",
        "Misfiling documents",
        "Being late",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Stealing post-it notes",
    },
    {
      id: 49,
      question: "What is the name of Jan's baby?",
      answers: ["Astrid", "Astria", "Aspen", "Alice"],
      correctAnswer: "Astrid",
    },
    {
      id: 50,
      question: "What tattoo does Andy get to make up for his mistake?",
      answers: ["Nard Dog", "A wolf", "A dolphin", "A dog"],
      correctAnswer: "Nard Dog",
    },
    {
      id: 51,
      question: "What does Dwight name his porcupine?",
      answers: ["Henrietta", "Madge", "Prickles", "Spike"],
      correctAnswer: "Henrietta",
    },
    {
      id: 52,
      question: "Who becomes the new manager after Michael leaves?",
      answers: ["Andy", "Dwight", "Robert California", "Gabe"],
      correctAnswer: "Andy",
    },
    {
      id: 53,
      question: "What does Angela keep in her filing cabinet?",
      answers: ["Cat food", "A baby", "A cat", "Knitting supplies"],
      correctAnswer: "A cat",
    },
    {
      id: 54,
      question:
        "What is the name of the song that Jim and Pam's wedding party dances down the aisle to?",
      answers: ["Forever", "Marry You", "You and Me", "At Last"],
      correctAnswer: "Forever",
    },
    {
      id: 55,
      question: "What does Kevin make for the office in Season 5?",
      answers: ["Chili", "Spaghetti", "Tacos", "Soup"],
      correctAnswer: "Chili",
    },
    {
      id: 56,
      question:
        "Who starts the Michael Scott Paper Company with Michael and Pam?",
      answers: ["Ryan", "Andy", "Jim", "Erin"],
      correctAnswer: "Ryan",
    },
    {
      id: 57,
      question: "What is the name of Dwight's cousin?",
      answers: ["Mose", "Zeke", "Jeb", "Rolf"],
      correctAnswer: "Mose",
    },
    {
      id: 58,
      question:
        "What does Michael eat instead of ice cream after breaking up with Carol?",
      answers: [
        "Mayonnaise and black olives",
        "Yogurt and sprinkles",
        "Ketchup and bread",
        "Mustard and pickles",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Mayonnaise and black olives",
    },
    {
      id: 59,
      question: "What does Michael say that everyone calls him?",
      answers: [
        "World's Best Boss",
        "Michael Scott",
        "The Office Leader",
        "Michael the Magic",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "World's Best Boss",
    },
    {
      id: 60,
      question: "What does Jim hide in Jell-O as a prank on Dwight?",
      answers: ["Stapler", "Phone", "Calculator", "Pen"],
      correctAnswer: "Stapler",
    },
  ],
};
